What we just introduced was a relatively simple
deployment process
is a relatively basic process
because the demo application we selected
Its functionality is relatively simple.
However, in real-world scenarios
In fact, there are many products nowadays
all require the integration of AI large model capabilities
we will explain to you
how to build upon the existing foundational workflows
to make some advancements and optimizations
The most straightforward way to introduce large AI models
this capability solution
is to call the online large model service
the process of invoking the online large model service
or this solution
this capability
integrate into our existing application code
Here we continue using the official case provided by Google
to illustrate
For example, let's continue to find one of these
For example, let's switch to the gallery section here
you can see more of these uh
the sample applications provided by the official
For example, let's select this SVG generator here
Let's click in to take a look at this application
The main functionality of this application is
it generates this SVG image based on your input
and it also supports download
this is such a simple capability
So we can actually see that
let's take a look at the code
Actually, we can know that behind the scenes
it's actually calling the Gemini 3
GEMINI 3 Pro Preview's large model
the ability to create images
So that's how such an online invocation process works
It's a very simple pure frontend application
the main calling logic is
it's stored in the frontend
in the service.ts frontend file
It can be seen that the environment variables are being referenced here
the Gemini API key
That is to say, when the image generation capability is needed
via this API key
to call Google's online image generation service
For such projects,
if we still use the method we demonstrated earlier, uh,
the process of deploying with three tools and three steps
There is a potential risk that in the code
will directly write the API key into the code
The resulting consequence is
your API key will be exposed
After we deploy this application
when others access our service through this domain name
For example,
As long as they right-click
then click here to inspect its source code
it can find it in the webpage's source code
in the front-end source code
find this API key in the frontend code
This API key can indeed be exposed.
If they use this API key to call the online services
that will be charged to your account
so when we deploy
Always maintain this sense of risk awareness
confidential account information such as API keys
information-type data
cannot be directly exposed to the outside
So how can we solve this issue?
The fundamental reason for this issue to arise is
The fundamental reason for this issue is
We have written the account information in the front-end code.
right
One approach to solve this issue
is to separate the frontend from the code that calls the large model capability
extract this piece of code
do not place it in the frontend
So here we introduce a method
through this project
the demonstration process of this project
add a lightweight backend system to it
move the step of calling the large model to the backend for execution
the API key in use can be hidden
Let me briefly demonstrate how to do this.
The first step is
we still go
save the project code to GitHub
Also, we need to, uh, come up with a name.
Give a name to this project
for example, let's call it deploy_svg
Generator
Then, uh, deploy it.
Then set the permission of the following project to private.
Then click to create the project
then push it to
Push it to the remote GitHub platform.
In this way, we can proceed as before
Click on this link to access the current project's
to this GitHub repository
Now, this operation
it's a bit different from the previous process
because in this process
We need to use a large model to assist us in secondary development.
So this development process
we cannot do this on the webpage anymore
We need to download it to local D
the code of this repository
Clone it locally for secondary development
But don't worry
this development process
We will let the large model assist us in completing it
Basically, there's no need to do the coding yourself, okay
or are not very familiar with the commands for managing code,
that is, for those who are not familiar with the git commands
So, uh, at the beginning when I introduced the preliminary preparations,
let everyone download the GitHub desktop client in advance
Let's open the GitHub desktop client
that is, the GitHub Desktop
For first-time users,
You may need to log in first
After logging in
When we are creating or cloning a new project,
you will be able to find the one we just mentioned in this list
the newly created deploy svg generator
this new project
We select the newly created project
Then confirm this local path
If there are no issues
you can click clone
Okay, now that the cloning is complete
we choose to
We choose to open the current project in VS Code
Ah, after opening it successfully,
you can see all the files on the left side
all the code files contained in this project
The first thing is to find the index.
the HTML file uh
Similarly, scroll to the bottom
add our initial step operation into it
This step still needs to be done.
Then,
we can proceed to make some slight modifications to this project
The purpose is to hide this API key.
The method is quite simple
let the large language model help us automatically add a lightweight backend to this project
a lightweight backend
Let's take a look at how I instructed the large model
Alright, I told the large model
Transform this project into a Next.js full-stack application
require the Gemini API key to be securely stored on the backend
then calling the AI's penetration capabilities in the backend
ensure that the API key I provided to you will not be leaked
So my goal is actually very clear.
The frontend is merely an information collection entry point
he hands over this task
the task of invoking this large model is handed over to the backend to handle
The backend won't be exposed, right?
This way my API key is secure.
and I asked him to use Next.js
to achieve frontend-backend interaction
Because it is a full-stack framework
can be used for both frontend development
can also be used to write backend code
Here, the large model I'm using for programming is Codex.
is one of the few large AI programming models that I personally find quite effective in practice.
one of the better-performing large models
Of course, you can also configure other large model services.
There's no problem at all.
OK, after entering this PROT
we click run
We can see the large model on the left side
gradually presents its transformation plan
as well as the progress of its execution
First of all, he is going to take this project
all the code is read in
Sigh
So why do we say using large models helps us automate
to code
it generally takes a longer time
because its context window is very long
So why in some large projects
The effectiveness of using large models for AI coding may not be so easy
or the effect may be relatively poor
or it might be more challenging to implement
a very clear reason
that is to say, it needs to dynamically identify
it
what information content needs to be included
This step is crucial.
Fortunately, next we can gradually see that
after the file
it will provide some operational steps
as well as some of the planning processes
This is actually a process of a small agent.
During the execution process
will also consider whether the previous step was executed correctly
all the changed content
are all displayed in this dialog box
This process is relatively slow
It will take a bit longer.
We can also skip it
Now you can see it's already displayed on the page
its plan and the progress bar of its execution
Currently, it has only reached the first stage.
This process might be a bit slow.
We can just skip it
until it completes execution
Let's take a look at its final effect